nfltraderumors.co 2014-06-25

# NFL Trade Rumors - | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

NFL Trade Rumors knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers NFL Trade Rumors’s treatment of personal information that NFL Trade Rumors gathers when you are on the NFL Trade Rumors website and when you useNFL Trade Rumors services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that NFL Trade Rumors does not own or control, or to individuals that NFL Trade Rumors does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by NFL Trade Rumors

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our NFL Trade Rumors users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. NFL Trade Rumors and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, NFL Trade Rumors cookie information, and the page you requested. NFL Trade Rumors uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
NFL Trade Rumors may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While NFL Trade Rumors will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

E-mail Communications  
NFL Trade Rumors is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. NFL Trade Rumors may send out e-mails with NFL Trade Rumors-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. NFL Trade Rumors cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of NFL Trade Rumors’s coolest features.

NFL Trade Rumors’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads.  If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.

Sharing Your Information

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

NFL Trade Rumors Personnel: NFL Trade Rumors personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of NFL Trade Rumors business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if NFL Trade Rumors, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of NFL Trade Rumors and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of NFL Trade Rumors, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: NFL Trade Rumors allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the NFL Trade Rumors website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the NFL Trade Rumors website. As a result, NFL Trade Rumors does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that NFL Trade Rumors has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using NFL Trade Rumors or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

NFL Trade Rumors may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the NFL Trade Rumors website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit NFL Trade Rumors website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 29th 2012 and last updated October 29th 2012.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at nfltraderumors@gmail.com.

At www.nfltraderumors.co, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.nfltraderumors.co and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.nfltraderumors.co makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.nfltraderumors.co does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.nfltraderumors.co.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.nfltraderumors.co and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Adbrite  
Burst Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.nfltraderumors.co send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.nfltraderumors.co has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.nfltraderumors.co’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
